<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FCM Viewer</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_error">Error</string>
    <string name="dialog_btn_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="dialog_msg_missing_gms">Please make sure your device has Google Play services installed</string>
    <string name="toolbar_search">Search</string>
    <string name="toolbar_exitSearch">Close</string>
    <string name="toolbar_more">More</string>
    <string name="toolbar_help">Help</string>
    <string name="toolbar_openGcmDiagnostics">FCM Diagnostics</string>
    <string name="toolbar_showSystemApp">Show System App</string>
    <string name="shortcut_shortlabel_GcmDiagnostics">FCM</string>
    <string name="shortcut_longlabel_GcmDiagnostics">FCM Diagnostics</string>
    <string name="shortcut_disable_GcmDiagnostics">FCM Unavailable</string>
    <string name="help_text">This APP can check which applications installed by users and system applications support Google FCM push, and can open the FCM system log page to view FCM connection status and application push records. \n
        After successfully connected to the FCM server, you also need to enable the auto-start permission of applications that support FCM \n
        (Customized roms in Mainland of China, except for a few whitelisted apps such as WeChat, will restrict application auto-start by default, and other versions of Android systems will not restrict it by default). \n
        You can click the application listed in the list to enter the system\'s application information page, click the \"Battery\" option, and make sure the status is \"Optimization\". \n
        When the status is \"Restricted\", FCM will not be able to pull up the application pop-up notification. This is FCM Determined by the principle, when a notification comes, FCM will broadcast and pull up the pop-up notification of the corresponding application. \n
        If the application is developed according to the specifications, when no message comes, the application will enter the cache in the background and will not consume a lot of power. </string>
</resources>